<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Musical Structure</string>

    <string name="activity_main_all_text">ALL SONGS\n\n\t
        The main activity of the application, and of course the launching screen.\n\t
        This Activity will contain the list (TextViews) of all songs in a vertical LinearLayout, wrapped in a ScrollView.\n\t
        Clicking a song (TextView) will open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        For demonstration I had put the listener on this TextView in order to open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a search widget (SearchView, not added because I suppose I am allowed only with TextViews and Buttons), which will allow the user to search through all the songs.\n\t
        The buttons at the bottom of the screen allows the user to navigate between activities (as suggested by buttons text).
    </string>

    <string name="activity_genres_text">GENRES\n\n\t
        This acitivty will have a parent vertical LinearLayout with multiple children verticals LinearLayout.\n\t
        Each children will contain 2 TextViews: one with the genre name (written with a draker and bigger font) and one with number of songs in the genre (written with smaller and lighter font, below the previous one).\n\t
        Clicking on the children LinearLayouts will open the GenreSelectedActivity.\n\t
        For demonstration I had put the listener on this TextView in order to open the GenreSelectedActivity.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a SearchView allowing to search by the genre name.\n\t
        The buttons at the bottom of the screen allows the user to navigate between activities (as suggested by buttons text).
    </string>

    <string name="activity_artists_text">ARTISTS\n\n\t
        This acitivty will have a parent vertical LinearLayout with multiple children verticals LinearLayout.\n\t
        Each children will contain 2 TextViews: one with the artists name (written with a draker and bigger font) and one with number of songs for that artist (written with smaller and lighter font, below the previous one).\n\t
        Clicking on the children LinearLayouts will open the ArtistSelectedActivity.\n\t
        For demonstration I had put the listener on this TextView in order to open the ArtistSelectedActivity.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a SearchView allowing to search by the artist name.
        The buttons at the bottom of the screen allows the user to navigate between activities (as suggested by buttons text).
    </string>

    <string name="activity_genre_selected_text">GENRE SELECTED\n\n\t
        This Activity will contain the list (TextViews) of all songs of theselected genre in a vertical LinearLayout, wrapped in a ScrollView.\n\t
        Clicking a song (TextView) will open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        For demonstration I had put the listener on this TextView in order to open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a SearchView allowing to search by the song name (only by this genre).
    </string>
    
    <string name="activity_artist_selected_text">ARTIST SELECTED\n\n\t
        This Activity will contain the list (TextViews) of all songs by the selected artist in a vertical LinearLayout, wrapped in a ScrollView.\n\t
        Clicking a song (TextView) will open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        For demonstration I had put the listener on this TextView in order to open the NowPlayingActivity.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a SearchView allowing to search by the song name (only by this artist).
    </string>

    <string name="now_playing_text">NOW PLAYING\n\n\t
        This Activity will contain a TextView with the name of song - name of artist.\n\t
        The Activity will have 3 buttons (previous, play/pause, next) centered both vertical and horizontal.\n\t
        In the upper right corner there will be a SearchView allowing to search through all the songs.
    </string>

    <string name="button_all_songs">All songs</string>
    <string name="button_genre_songs">Genres</string>
    <string name="button_artists_songs">Artists</string>
</resources>
